Next we come to shoes.
You are going to want a good sturdy shoe.
I mean this should be a shoe for a scarecrow.
It is a shoe you would go hiking in.
It is the shoe you would scale a mountain in.
Okay maybe not quite that extreme but close.
You definitely want an out doorsy strong shoe.
Colors of shoe that I prefer for a scarecrow are of course brown.
I mean you want colors warmer. Colors of the soil. Colors of the harvest. Even having some of lighter beige colors in there also could work.
Also again you don't want too loose kind of like the worker solid sturdy look of your shoe that you are going to be wearing as a scarecrow.
Some scarecrows don't have shoes as I have already said.
But of course you are not going to be walking around barefoot.
That would look a little bit funny.
And also you are going to want a shoe which has a higher top to it.
Why is that?
Low top shoes we are going to have some stuff coming out of the bottom of the pant leg that we are going to go into later.
You are going to want a high top to kind of catch that to help hold it.
You are also going to want to make sure that your ankle has a lot of stability and support because you don't want to turn it just because your legs a little bit more rumpled than normal.